Guide to the Garden Club of Allegheny County Records, 1913-2012 AIS.2006.07
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Ephemera and Media Material, 1914-2005; VI.
  - Newspaper Clippings and Scrapbooks, 1961-2003; 3.
    - GCA 2005 Annual Meeting Highlights Poster Photo of "Flower Show Winner at Kemper Museum" (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - GCA 2005 Annual Meeting Highlights Poster Photo of " 'All That Jazz,' Kemper Museum" (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - GCA 2005 Annual Meeting Highlights Poster Photo of "Behind the Scenes" (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - GCA 2005 Annual Meeting Highlights Poster Photo of "Public Gardens: Powell & Kauffman" (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - GCA 2005 Annual Meeting Highlights Poster Photo of "GCAC N. Clay & M.L. Majons" (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - "Haven for Songsters" Clipping (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - George Washington Meeting at Rolling Rock Club (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Margaret Pollard Rea Garden Photographs (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - Phipps Conservatory Exhibit (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - Photo of a Garden (Box 59, Folder 20)
    - Pittsburgh Information and Site Locator Pamphlet (Box 59, Folder 21)
    - Highland Park, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Schenley Park (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Homewood Garden Project, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Allegheny Commons (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Pizzazz, 2000, 2002-2003 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - GCA Warhol Exhibition, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Hat Luncheon, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Student Conservation Association Project, 2002 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Gardens Around Pittsburgh (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Horticultural Society/Botanical Society (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - GCA Trip to Hawaii and Japan, 1961 (Box 60, Folder 11)
- 2011 Additions, 1961-2010; VII.
  The records found in this series represent additions to the collection made by the Garden Club of Allegheny County from 2009-2011. Records types represented in this series are: meeting minutes, committee reports, officer reports, event and activities planning documents, awards and award applications, correspondence, and newspaper clippings.
  - Membership Meeting Minutes, 1989-1991 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Membership Meetings Photographs, 1992, 2000-2007 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Membership Meeting Minutes, 1992-1995 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Membership Meeting Minutes, 1995 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Membership Meeting Minutes, 1996 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Membership Meeting Minutes, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Membership Meeting Minutes, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Membership Meeting Minutes, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Membership Meeting Minutes, 2000 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Membership Meeting Minutes, 2001 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Membership Meeting Minutes, 2003-2004 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Membership Meeting Agendas, 2008-2010 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1989-1990 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1991-1992 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1993-1995 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1996 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 2000 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 2001 (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 2001-2002 (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 2003-2004 (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Board of Directors Meeting Agendas, 2008-2010 (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes (bound book), June 13, 1988- June 16, 1994 (Box 62, Volume 1)
  - General Meeting Records and Reports, 2001-2002 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Zone V Meeting, 1994-1995 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Zone V Meeting, GCAC Annual Summary, 2004-2010 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Zone V Mini-Meeting Programs, 2005, 2007 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Zone V Annual Meeting, 2008 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Zone V Mini-Meeting, 2009 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Annual Meeting and Reports, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Annual Meeting and Reports, 1995-2000 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Annual Meeting Photographs (taken at Peggy McKnight's home), June 11, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Annual Meeting Photographs (taken at Mrs. Pete Cole's home), June 2004 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Annual Meeting and Reports, 2008-2009 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Annual Meeting and Reports, 2009-2010 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Accounts Statement of Activity Reports, 1989-1995 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1991-1994 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1995 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1996 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1997 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 2001 (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 2000-2002 (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 2003-2004 (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Slides of Members, 1961 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Slides of Members at Meetings, 1961 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Membership Meeting Attendance Reports, 1991-1992 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Membership Meeting Attendance Reports, 2002-2004 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Membership Invitation Letter (Sample), 2007 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Membership Questionnaire, 2009 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Archives Committee, 2004 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Committee and Officers List, 1990-1994 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Committee List, 2008-2010 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Long Range Planning Committee- Funding Application Procedure and Schedule, 2004 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Long range Planning Committee- Native Trees to the Western Allegheny Plateau, 2008 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Nominating Committee- Club Member Profile Form, undated (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Program Committee, 1995-1998 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Program Committee Guidelines, 1998-1999 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Program Committee, 2003-2004 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Public Relations Committee Chairman Job Description, 2006 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Workshops Committee Reports, 2003 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Assorted President's Notes, 1997-2000 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - President Sally Foster's Papers, 2002-2003 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - President Mary Odom Addresses, 2007 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - President's Meeting, 2008 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Flower Show Slides, 1953 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Slides of Flower Show Prize Winners, 1960, 1961 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Flower Show Slide Carousel Disc, ca.1960s (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Flower Show Arrangement Slides, 1961 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Flower Show Entries Slides, March 1965 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Garden Club Room Spring Show at the Phipps Conservatory, 1965 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - New York Flower Show Entries Slides, 1966 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - "In the Spirit of Old Economy Village" Flower Show Program, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - GCAC Flower Shows, 1989-1990 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Garden Club of America Flower Show Manual, 1996 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - GCAC at Philadelphia Flower Show, 1998-1999, 2006 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Garden Club of America Flower Show Manual (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Lil Fisher at the GCAC Flower Show at the Mellon Bank Building Photo, 1990 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - "Possession Obsession" Flower Show Brochures, 2002 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - "Possession Obsession" Show Entries, 2002 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - "Possession Obsession" Flower Show Judges Panel and Awards, 2002 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - "Possession Obsession" Flower Show Publicity, 2002 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - "Possession Obsession" Flower Show Nametag, 2002 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - "Possession Obsession" Articles, 2002 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - "Our Living Rivers" Exhibit at Flower Show, 2002 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - "Possession Obsession" Flower Show Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Village Garden Club of Sewickley "In the Studio" Flower Arranging Workshop and Flower Show, April 18-19, 2002 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Garden Club of America Flower Show and Judging Guide, 2000 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - GCAC Flower Show "Zen and the Art of Gardening", 2005 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - "Grow Your Own" Garden Club of America Flower Show Manual, undated (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - "Name It!: Demystifying Nomenclature for Entry Cards in Flower Shows", undated (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Zone V Mini-Meeting Award Ceremony Photos, October 20, 1999 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Letters of Recommendation for Sherley Blaxter for Living Treasure Award, 2001 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Zone V Dorothy Flacon Platt Award, 2002 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Mary Louise Gaillot Receiving an Award Photos, ca. 2006 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Jeanie Robinson giving Martha Robinson and Betty Dones the Living Treasure Award Photo, undated (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Phipps Conservatory and Botanical Gardens Flora Award Enamel Box, 2000 (Box 67, Object 1)
  - Garden Club of America Public Relations Award Submission Portfolio, 2007 (Map-case 9-4)
  - Beechwood Farms Christmas Workshop Photos, 2002 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Charleston, South Carolina GCAC Garden Tour Trip Album, March 31 -April 3, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 2-38)
  - Christmas Packages Wrapping Slides, December 9, 1960 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Christmas Wreath Workshop Photos, December 11, 2003 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Closing of Outdoor Garden at Phipps Conservatory, October 18, 2004 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Entrance Corridor Botanic Garden of Western Pennsylvania Landscape Master Plan, 2007 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Fallingwater Tour Photos and Slides, 1964 (Box 69, Folder 5-6)
  - GCAC Activities, 2003 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - GCAC Members at Various Club Activities, undated (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Ken Druse Lecture, 2004 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - May Market Photo, 1951 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - May Market Slides, 1961 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - May Market Photos, 2001 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - May Market Slides, 2005 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - May Market Photos, undated (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Medicinal Garden Signage at Phipps Conservatory Photos, November 11, 1999 (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - New Member Orientation at Allegheny Common Photos, July 27, 1999 (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - New Member Orientation Photo, 2001 (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - Northside Post Office, before planting Project Photos, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - Old Economy Village GCAC Lunch Slides, 1961 (Box 69, Folder 19)
  - Old Economy Village Gardens Slides, August 1963 (Box 69, Folder 20)
  - Old Economy Village Greenhouse Slides, March 19, 1964 (Box 69, Folder 21)
  - Outdoor Garden at Phipps Conservatory Slides, June 9, 1981 (Box 69, Folder 22)
  - Phipps Conservatory Outdoor Garden Album, 1987-1988 (Box 69, Folder 23-30)
  - Phipps Conservatory Outdoor Garden Album, 1987-1988, 1990-1992, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 1-12)
  - Phipps Conservatory Outdoor Garden Photos, October 11, 1999 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Pittsburgh Parks Conservancy, 2002 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Pizzazz Financial Information, 1995 (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Pizzazz Invitations, 1995 (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - Pizzazz Vendors, 1995 (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - Pizzazz Benefit for Botany in Action Fact Sheet, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - Pizzazz Financial Information, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - Pizzazz Photos, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 20)
  - Pizzazz Press Releases and Flyers, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 21)
  - Pizzazz Vendors, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 22)
  - Pizzazz Events Notes for Next Year, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 23)
  - Pizzazz Invitations, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 24)
  - Pizzazz at Pittsburgh Golf Club Function Prospectus and Layout, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 25)
  - Pizzazz Preview Party, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 26)
  - Pizzazz Publicity and Invitations, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 27)
  - Pizzazz Vendor Contracts, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 28)
  - Pizzazz Vendor Information, 1997 (Box 70, Folder 29)
  - Pizzazz Brochures and Poster, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 30)
  - Pizzazz Committee List, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 31)
  - Pizzazz Correspondence with Fox Chapel Golf Club, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 32)
  - Pizzazz Donation List and Letters, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 33)
  - Pizzazz layout and Equipment List, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 34)
  - Pizzazz Marketing, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 35)
  - Pizzazz Photos, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 36)
  - Pizzazz Preview Luncheon, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 37)
  - Pizzazz Raffle, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 38)
  - Pizzazz Vendor Contracts, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 39)
  - Pizzazz Vendor Invoices, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 40)
  - Pizzazz Vendors, 1998 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Pizzazz Committee Meetings, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Pizzazz Financial Reports, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Pizzazz Hosting and Housing Committee, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Pizzazz Invitations, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Pizzazz Layout and Tent, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Pizzazz Mailings and Printed Materials, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Pizzazz Notes, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Pizzazz Patrons, Donors, and Benefactors, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Pizzazz Photos, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Pizzazz Preview Party, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Pizzazz Vendor Contracts, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Pizzazz Vendor Information, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Pizzazz Committee, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Pizzazz Financial Reports, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Pizzazz Floor Plan, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Pizzazz Housing and Hospitality Committee, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Pizzazz Invitations, Flyers, and Posters, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Pizzazz Mailings, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Pizzazz Preview Party, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Pizzazz Reports, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Pizzazz Vendor Contracts, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - Pizzazz Vendor Exit Surveys, 2000 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - Pizzazz Vendor Information, 2000 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Pizzazz Financial Report and Information, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Pizzazz Flyers, Invitations, and other printed material, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Pizzazz Invoices, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Pizzazz Reports and Notes, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Pizzazz Vendor Contracts, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Pizzazz Vendor Exit Surveys, 2001 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Pizzazz Financial Summary, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Pizzazz Invitations and Flyers, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Pizzazz Invoices, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Pizzazz Preview Party, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Pizzazz Preview Party Photos, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Pizzazz Program Layout, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 13)
  - Pizzazz Reports, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 14)
  - Pizzazz Tickets, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Pizzazz Vendor Contracts, 2002 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Pizzazz Vendor Exit Surveys, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Pizzazz Media Kit for Whirl Magazine, 2002 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Pizzazz Corporate Sponsors, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Pizzazz Financial Reports and Statements, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Pizzazz Fox Chapel Golf Club Layout, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Pizzazz Housing Committee, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Pizzazz Donors and Benefactors, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Pizzazz Invitations and Flyers, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Pizzazz Reports and Committees, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Pizzazz Speakers, Special Guests, and Vendors, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Pizzazz Tickets, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Pizzazz Vendor Contracts, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 12-13)
  - Pizzazz Vendor Exit Surveys, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Pizzazz Reports on CD-ROM, 2003-2005 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Pizzazz Financial Report and Summary, 2004 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Pizzazz Floor Layout, 2004 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Pizzazz Hospitality Committee, 2004 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Pizzazz Housing Committee, 2004 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Pizzazz Invoices, 2004 (Box 74, Box 1)
  - Pizzazz Information on Similar Benefit Vendor Shows, 2004-2007 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Pizzazz Merchandise Models, 2004 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Pizzazz Donors and Benefactors, 2004 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Pizzazz Invitations and Flyers, 2004 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Pizzazz Photographs Proofs, 2004 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Pizzazz Preview Party and Thursday Night Events, 2004 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Pizzazz Printing and Mail Services, 2004 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Pizzazz Programs and Invitations, 2004 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Pizzazz Publicity Committee, 2004 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Pizzazz Reports and Timelines, 2004 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Pizzazz Speaker, Ron Morgan, 2004 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Pizzazz Sponsors and Underwriting, 2004 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Pizzazz Tickets, 2004 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Pizzazz Timeless Treasures Booth, 2004 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Pizzazz Vendor Contracts, 2004 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Pizzazz Vendor Equipment Needs, 2004 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Pizzazz Vendor Information, 2004 (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Pizzazz Volunteer Committee, 2004 (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Pizzazz Financial Reports and Summary, 2005 (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - Pizzazz Housing and Hospitality Committee, 2005 (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - Pizzazz Invitations and Flyers, 2005 (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - Pizzazz Patrons and Benefactors, 2005 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Pizzazz Photos, 2005 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Pizzazz Press Releases, 2005 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Pizzazz Preview party, 2005 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Pizzazz Printing and Mailing Services, 2005 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Pizzazz Programs and Invitations, 2005 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Pizzazz Publicity Committee, 2005 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Pizzazz Reports and Committees, 2005 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Pizzazz Vendors, 2005 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Pizzazz Vendor Contracts, 2005 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Pizzazz Vendor Equipment Needs, 2005 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Pizzazz Vendor Surveys, 2005 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Pizzazz Advertisements, 2006 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Pizzazz Benefactors and Sponsors, 2006 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Pizzazz (CD), 2006 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Pizzazz Financial Summary and Information, 2006 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Pizzazz Floor Plans, 2006 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Pizzazz Housing Committee, 2006 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Pizzazz Information, 2006 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Pizzazz Invitations, Flyers, Programs, and Tickets, 2006 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Pizzazz Long Range Planning, 2006 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Pizzazz Printing Sources and Proofs, 2006 (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Pizzazz Programs and Invitations, 2006 (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Pizzazz Public Relations Committee, 2006 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Pizzazz Publicity, 2006 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Pizzazz Reports and Committees, 2006 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Pizzazz Signage Designs (CD), 2006 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Pizzazz Vendors, 2006 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Pizzazz Vendor Contracts, 2006 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Pizzazz Vendor Equipment Needs, 2006 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Pizzazz Vendor Information, 2006 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Pizzazz Vendor Survey, 2006 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Pizzazz Benefactors, Patrons, and Sponsors, 2007 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Pizzazz Committee Reports and Meeting Minutes, 2007 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Pizzazz Financial Summary and Information, 2007 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Pizzazz Floor Plan and Layout, 2007 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Pizzazz Fox Chapel Golf Club, 2007 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Pizzazz Printing Services, 2007 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Pizzazz Publicity, 2007 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Pizzazz Program, Save the Date cards, and Invitations, 2007 (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Pizzazz Public Relations Committee, 2007 (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - Pizzazz Vendors, 2007 (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - Pizzazz Contracts, 2007 (Box 76, Folder 20)
  - Pizzazz Vendor Equipment Needs, 2007 (Box 76, Folder 21)
  - Pizzazz Committee Meetings, 2008 (Box 76, Folder 22)
  - Pizzazz Committee Reports, 2008 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Pizzazz Community Focus Project- Frick Environmental Center Landscape Design, 2008 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Pizzazz Floor Plan Layout, 2008 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Pizzazz Invitations, 2008 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Pizzazz Invoices, 2008 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Pizzazz Marketing Partnership, 2008 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Pizzazz Photos (CD), 2008 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Pizzazz Press Kit, 2008 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Pizzazz Press Releases, 2008 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Pizzazz Program, Save the Date cards and Invitations, 2008 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Pizzazz Public Relations Committee, 2008 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Pizzazz Public Relations Media Contacts, 2008 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Pizzazz Vendors, 2008 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Pizzazz Vendor Contracts, 2008 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Pizzazz Vendor Surveys, 2008 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Pizzazz Programs, Save the Date cards, and Invitations, 2010 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Riverlife (CD), undated (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Scholarships, 1996 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Scholarships, 2007 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Settler's Cabin Park Wildflower Hike Photos, April 2006 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - Women's Land Army Photo, undated (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - "The World of Exteriors" John Danzer Lecture, 2009-2010 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - Snowden, ca. 1960s (Box 78, Reel 1-3)
  - Horticulture Committee Reports, 2002-2003 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Horticulture Committee Meeting Photos (at Donna Catone's home), January 2006 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Assorted Correspondence, 2007-2010 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Pizzazz Newspaper Clippings, 1996 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Pizzazz Newspaper Clippings, 1997 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Pizzazz Newspaper Clippings, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Pizzazz Newspaper Clippings, 1999 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Pizzazz Newspaper Clippings, 2000 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Pizzazz Newspaper Clippings, 2001 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Pizzazz Newspaper Clippings, 2002 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Pizzazz Newspaper Clippings, 2003 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Pizzazz Newspaper Clippings, 2004 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Pizzazz Newspaper Clippings, 2005 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Pizzazz Newspaper Clippings, 2006 (Box 79, Folder 14-15)
  - Pizzazz Newspaper Clippings, 2007 (Box 80, Folder 1-2)
  - Pizzazz Newspaper Clippings, 2008 (Box 80, Folder 3-4)
  - Pizzazz Newspaper Clippings, 2010 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Barbara Milo Ohrbach Event, 2000 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Old Economy Revitalization Newspaper Clipping, 2000 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Botanic Gardens of Western Pennsylvania Clipping (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - GCAC Members at Phipps Conservatory Outdoor Garden Newspaper Clipping, undated (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Photographic Diary of the GCA trip to Japan, May 1961 (Box 81, Volume 1)
- 2012-2013 Additions, 1934-2012; VIII.
  This series represents additions made to the collection by the Garden Club of Allegheny County in 2012 and 2013. It includes meeting minutes, bylaws, photographs, membership information, activity and event documentation, awards, and officer reports.
  - Annual Committee Reports, 1981-1988 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Annual Meeting Photos, 2002 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Annual Meeting and Reports, 2003-2004 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Annual Meeting and Reports, 2004-2005 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Archives Committee, 2003-2006 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Awards Certificates (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Awards Committee Reports, 2000-2002 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Awards Committee Report, 2003-2004 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Awards Committee Report, 2004-2005 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Awards Committee Report, 2005-2006 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Awards Committee Report, 2006-2007 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Awards Committee Report, 2007-2008 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Awards Committee Report, 2008-2009 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Awards Committee Report, 2010-2012 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Awards History, 2001-2006 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Board Meeting Agendas, 2004-2006 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Board of Directors meeting Minutes, 2004-2006 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - By-laws, 1980-1982 (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - By-laws, 1991 (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - Carrie T. Watson Proposal for Membership (Box 82, Folder 20)